The sun is of his arms and continues
NAN DEMO A NAN DEMO A NAN DEMO A
FUN
Vison in the cold Eddie
Numbering in the dark side
The immortal 0 skin
started the
photo
комментар
i
picture
can
you
i
the
hair
i
yeah
wow
Hope book 描き出す 光
花色の明日が呼んでる
道しるってなくたって
不安なら分け合って
君がいるいつだって
ほら笑って
High five!
夜中心
間奏
カセット
エンド
ライト
All right, we're in the final stretch now.
Looks like everybody's pretty hyped up about it this year.
Still got to rainbow up our rose, so we need to work quick.
Right.
It looks all muddy.
It's multicolored, so the colors bled more than they should have.
Should we hit up a florist?
But a real rainbow rose costs over a thousand yen.
Maybe we can mask certain parts?
Hey, found you, Maureen.
Oh, wait, you're in your uniform.
Karin.
Aw, no suit yet.
Anna, looks like your boobs are out and about again.
My boobs?
Noah said.
Her suit looks so cool,
plus her undies made her titties disappear!
Apparently.
Wow, Noah sucks at explaining things.
Hmm.
Maybe it'll work better if I just paint it by hand.
You're doing great, Gojo.
Whoa, is that Reisama's rose?
Oh, yeah.
Aw, looks like it didn't turn on his plan.
Because there are a ton of colors.
Makes it pretty hard to do right.
Actually, I know how to make a rainbow rose if you need help.
Hmm.
Huh?
Yep, yep.
I know exactly how to do it.
Please, we were not for you to teach us!
Of course.
Don't gotta be so feral.
Hmm, oh, looks like they actually sell some nearby.
Okay, I'mma go shopping real quick,
so wait for me in the chem room.
Why the chem room?
I'm back!
Welcome back!
That was fast.
I ran so fast, I'm a little toasty.
Is that... a real flour?
Yep, 200 yen.
Okay, here we go.
First, you cut the stem.
Ha-ha!
Then you mix up the food coloring.
Mix!
Then you put in the stem that's been cut.
And make sure the whole thing doesn't fall over.
Shhh!
And tomorrow you'll have your very own rainbow rose
for a big cosplay!
Seriously?
It's that easy?
Yep.
Even though it's a real rose,
it should last through the pageant.
How do you know how to make these anyway?
Back in grade school,
I made one for my independent research project.
You... you really saved us.
Thanks for your help.
Aww.
No need for the drama.
I just taught you what I knew.
Seriously.
I was about to buy another fake flower
and paint each petal individually by hand.
Individually?
Oh...
So... then...
Does that mean I totally saved your guys' butts with this?
You betcha!
You're the best, Sarah!
Ooh! Glad to help!
Having people ask for your help is super nice,
don't you agree?
Yay!
I'm home!
Thanks for having me!
Ah, welcome home.
Dinner's just about ready.
You're the master chef tonight, Gramps?
That's a first for me!
You must be tired getting ready for the festival.
I'll handle cooking till it's done.
Huh?
Wow, thank you.
Mm-hmm.
I've always been nervous to ask anyone for help
because I didn't want to burden them with my problems.
I worried they'd resent me for it.
But I was the one making things harder
by assuming how other people would feel
before even asking them.
Maybe it's okay for things to be simpler from now on.
But...
This sucks.
We were absolutely crushing it this morning too.
Class three's smokin' us.
Ugh, this sucks.
We were absolutely crushing it this morning, too.
Class three's smoking us.
Well, the smell of curry is bound to draw a crowd at lunchtime.
Hard to turn down rice when you're hungry.
Kitsukawa, you sound like some guy on the baseball team.
Koga, Kensei, time to switch out brakes.
Yeah.
You'll switch out in a bit, too, Kitsukawa.
Okay.
Also, Gojo, you haven't eaten yet, have you?
Oh, I forgot.
Yeah, those of us in the classroom had a feeling you hadn't, so take this, okay?
Eat it when you have a sec.
Any updates, man?
Class three is owning us.
If I'm being real here, we're probably losing again.
Our line's crazy long.
Ugh, seriously?
Man, Kashiwagi, you don't pull punches, do you?
Yeah, he's always been harsh like that.
It's part of his charm.
What?
We can't ignore the gravity of the situation.
We've got to get more barkers and kick this shit into high gear.
Ain't no way I'm throwing in the towel already.
Oh, who we fighting?
You better believe we haven't given up either.
I'm heading out.
Gojo, you'd better eat.
You his mom?
Oh, Kashiwagi.
Hmm?
Thanks a lot for the food.
They've got it rough.
Seems like it.
But I'm sure they'll be fine.
Huh?
You seem pretty sure about that.
Well, of course I am.
Everyone's working super hard, and I'm gonna take first place in the pageant.
In the show, Rae Sama always puts herself last in order to make sure every one of her princesses' dreams comes true.
That's something I really love about her.
So I mean it when I say I want nothing more than for her to be happy.
The princesses who visit her all work hard to make Rae the number one host.
The reason we love Prez Hosts as much as we do is because everyone's so supportive of one another no matter what.
So that's why I'll win first place for everyone.
There's no way we'll lose.
I'll be up on that stage decked out in this cosplay you put your heart into with the perfect makeup you did.
I'm definitely going to win first place.
I made it just in time.
Sorry.
The line's been out the door all day.
All good.
Oh, is it done?
Yep.
Oh my gosh, this is absolute perfection!
I'm fine if people come in when we put on the outfit.
But when it comes to her makeup, I need to concentrate so my hands are steady.
Kitagawa, let's get started on your makeup right away.
Okay.
Maureen, how goes the prep girl?
You all finished with your makeup?
Don't look it.
It's been five ever since you worn contacts.
Yeah, it's been a while, huh?
Yes, I made it before you finished!
Gojo, do you mind if I watch?
Sorry, Gojo.
She's our last hope of winning first place, so we're counting on you.
Uh, right.
Murakami, you wanted to watch, yeah?
Koga?
Huh?
Hey, Gojo!
Gojo!
I'm so excited.
Right?
Huh?
I picked the sewing practice room because no one comes in here, so why?
Cosplay makeup is totally different from regular makeup, right?
I can't wait to see how it's done.
Yeah, I was curious about that too.
Calm down.
Deep breaths.
I need to hurry.
I only have an hour to finish everything.
Drums here and I'm the appetizer.
We bought a bunch of stuff, so let's all eat together.
We got you two food that you can eat one-handed.
Thanksies!
The cosplay event had a lot of people too, but I could kind of concentrate then.
I need to get it together and focus.
I have to do my best.
If I mess this up, then...
mess up.
We're counting on you!
Do your best, dude!
You're the only one who can make the outfit, Gojo.
Ain't no way I'm throwing in the towel already!
Everyone's putting their all into winning first place.
If I screw this up, we'll lose.
It'll be my fault.
Gojo?
You okay?
I'll be up on that stage, decked out in this cosplay you put your heart into,
with the perfect makeup you did.
I'm definitely going to win first place.
Yes!
I'm not all going to win first place.
This work.
So I'm glad that you like them.
Very glad.
You do an incredible job.
You have to know that, right?
It feels good when my work is complemented,
but that can't be the reason I do it.
Though I fear the real reason I keep pushing is equally as shallow.
I can't let them down.
I was put here to make Rey shine.
It's my duty.
I understand now.
This is my role.
I was put here to help Kitagawa shine.
To help her get first.
For her, I'll make it happen no matter what.
With these two hands,
I'll do my best so she can do hers.
We'll do this.
Let's get here.
Thank you.
Take care.
Bye-bye.
Amen.
Thank you very much.
Well, Madame Brett, how do you feel?
I'm having a lot of fun.
Bet you are.
Let's keep the ball rolling, shall we?
Next up is entry number 11 from Class 1-5.
It's Maureen Kitagawa.
Ta-da!
Wait.
Rei-sama!
Sure sounds like the ladies like her.
Her school's hottest guy in a guy!
I can die happy.
Oh, right!
One, two...
Party for the win!
Rei-sama, it's like she stepped out of the anime.
I need to calm down.
I have to be a fair judge!
That's the loudest you've cheered.
Good grief, I need some earplugs.
You must be Rei-sama from Press Host, yeah?
I'm begging to the idol scene, so when I saw Yuichi was playing Koyomi in the drama, I had to watch it.
Good for you!
How do you do it, Kitagawa?
You're always so dazzling.
Like a shining star.
Is that radiant something she was born with?
Her fair skin, her fair skin, her big eyes, her little nose, her lips, those slender fingers.
I can't look away.
Whatever this feeling is, I can't fight it.
It's coming from deep inside my soul.
It's new.
But for some reason, it's so familiar.
Her costume is spectacular!
She's... just so.
Is there anything specific you'd like to call our attention to?
Piu?
Everything that you see is the work of Wakana Gojo.
Very nice!
Thanks for the insider scoop!
Last but not least, it's time for you to turn on the charm!
Follow me!
Following you!
Ready?
Ready!
One, two, here we go!
This pageant is heating up now!
Your princess is heating up now!
My hostess are singing live to you.
Singing with Chris Class 1-5-3.
And he hosts Fury out loud and crowd.
Let's get some nice.
Let's slay this crowd.
So tell you next time it's nice.
tonight cause host boys working hard tonight go find her princess take a hand get her so hot that
she can't stand treat her like a queen treat her like a toy fill her head with dreams and heart
with hope and joy darkest hour of night who is it she wants she wants the hottest host in town
from class one five oh she wants me number one so make me number one we live happily ever after
princess and host princess vote for me all i want is to be your number one yoisho
okay yoisho
ah what a day we crushed the other classes in the pageant and won first place overall hip hip
you two are totally going down in school history for this
you're like class celebs i was moved to freaking tears dude we're surrounded yay i'm glad you liked it
that's an understatement i still don't get how a couple teensy pieces of tape transformed your eyes
same it's practically makeup magic the champagne call was genius it really brought right alive
big time if i make karaoke reservations would you all be down to party there yeah
a party you're coming aren't you gojo huh uh well it was kitagawa who won the pageant for us
and i didn't have time to help with the decoration because i was busy fixing the suit
i don't deserve to what are you talking about we can't party without the star of the show
the pageant was the only reason we beat class three without you we would have been toast bro
you have to come gojo i have like a bajillion makeup questions to ask you say you'll come with man
i didn't know you used a special eyeshadow that you can't sweat off i needed that at the sports
festival most other guys wouldn't get this but sometimes i feel like i care about sumugi's
happiness as much as i do my own dude i totally feel that you guys hungry for anything else a melon soda
cola and potentially some food can i please see that this song is a marine special
i needed a break oh hey you vanished so i thought you went home and i freaked the freak out
so sorry i'm not quite used to places like this i needed a breather i gotcha
don't you think all your friends in there are wondering where you are nah those goobers have sick
karaoke songs and yummy soda to worry about nobody is gonna care if we take a much needed time out
i guess you're right the cultural festival was a blast i'm wiped though same
it was pretty hard but it was worth it
you did an awesome job you really became the character this time the way you pulled her
in with your hand on her back was the perfect balance of care and force
right um actually i've reduced a pull of the waist is the quickest way to make a girl's heart skip a beat
you okay okay yep of course i uh i yeah this place is really impressive looks like they have a lot
more to offer than just karaoke you've never been here no then we've got to check out the arcade
you sure it's all right if i keep it yeah of course rage got the best of my wallet
i'm so happy hey next do you wanna
come to think of it i have some good pictures of him but none of us
what's up uh if it's cool i'd like to get a picture together i mean it's purikura totes casual
you down yeah sure dude huh you're here too we were gonna go bowling and then we saw you two hanging
out hey boys kitagawa wants to take some pics i guess that's fine i'm done if she insists i don't
insist get lost i didn't ask for this are you ready for your close-up i've never done this before
well i'm no pro same here so you mean i'm not alone the only way to improve is by practicing right
good point can it even fit five yeah definitely once you're ready press the take photo button
and to think we still have to bowl
bye
hey
Thank you.